# Kristian Adi

# Front End-Developer

I am graduated as electrical engineering and have 6 years of experiences in related field. As engineer I aware that internet technology is constantly evolving, so I decided to learn about web development. I took some IBM certificate course by Coursera, got certified, and became skilled in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React and more. Currently, I'm focusing on enhancing my Front-End skills. Through practices, I've gained confidence in my learning abilities and technical skills, beside using my abilities to help people who need my merit, I believe I can be fit with your organization's vision and goals.



⊠ kristian.adi.p7@gmail.com





Jakarta, Indonesia

# **Area of Expertise**



# **Experience**

## Front-End Developer

Sept 2023 - Now (3 months)

- I studied as a Fullstack Developer from course had some certified about Cloud Computing, Front end developer and etc.
- Build some project website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.

## **Electrical Engineer**

# SANGO CERAMICS INDONESIA Company

Dec 2016 - Jul 2023 (6 years 8 months)

- Fix, build and modified production machines to make production continues.
- Build and modified some machine and made it more efective, eficient and save to workers.
- Ensure that every electrical wiring, tools and line is located, tidy, protected and save from and for workers.

#### **Assistant Lecturer**

#### Polytechnic Mechatronics of Sanata Dharma

Aug 2013 - Dec 2016 (3 years 5 months)

- Teach some practice subject of Mechatronics to college students (ex Robotics, Basic Electrical, pneumatic and hidraulic, PLC, etc.
- Giving simple and easy understanding explanation to students about the subjects.
- Bring a review, score and evaluation for student project results.

#### Intern

#### Dua Kelinci Company

Jan 2012 - Mar 2012 (2 months)

- Maintenance some production machines and learn about production line system.
- Ensure that electrical wiring and line is protected and save for workers.

### **Education**



#### Coursera

Computer Software Engineering

2023 - Now

I took a learn as Full Stack Developer, but I finish in some month to be Front-End Developer, and I want to grow my skill first as It.



## Sanata Dharma University

Bachelor of Science, Electrical and Electronics Engineering

2012 - 2015

Associated Degree of Mechatronics

2009 - 2012

I learn two of Electrical application, at the first three years as associate degree I learn about automatication as Mechatronics subject, and the next to Bachelor I learn about Electrical Engineering

### **Licenses & Certifications**

- IBM Introduction to Cloud Computing Coursera Course Certificates
- IBM Getting Started with Git and GitHub Coursera Course Certificates
- IBM Introduction to Web Development with HTML, CSS, JavaScript Coursera Course Certificates
- IBM Developing Front-End Apps with React Coursera Course Certificates
- IBM Developing Back-End Apps with Node.Js and Express Coursera Course Certificates
- IBM Python for Data Science, Al & Development Coursera Course Certificates
- Tae Kwon Do turnament Certificates as participant

# Language

- English Intermediate
- Indonesian Fluent